ILGWU 35mm Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N35
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU 35mm Negatives of Photographs
1960-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 P N35
14 cubic feet
3.2 linear ft.
Photographs, negatives (photographic).
7461856
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 19, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780 P: ILGWU Photographs 5780 PNGP: ILGWU Glass Plate Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45: ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs
Clothing workers -- Labor unions; Textile workers -- Labor unions
7461856
- negatives 211A-238A (Box 1, Folder 1)
- negatives 239A-268A (Box 2, Folder 1)
- negatives 268A-315A (Box 3, Folder 1)
- negatives 316A-353S (Box 4, Folder 1)
- negatives 355A-383E (Box 5, Folder 1)
- negatives 383G-406B (Box 6, Folder 1)
- negatives 406C-444C (Box 7, Folder 1)
- negatives 444D-472B (Box 8, Folder 1)
- negatives 472C-501B (Box 9, Folder 1)
- negatives 502A-518B (Box 10, Folder 1)
- negatives 518C-526H (Box 11, Folder 1)
- negatives 526J-568E (Box 12, Folder 1)
- negatives 568F-595C (Box 13, Folder 1)
- negatives 597A-624B (Box 14, Folder 1)
- negatives 624D-654H (Box 15, Folder 1)
- negatives 655A-690G (Box 16, Folder 1)
- negatives 693B-734B (Box 17, Folder 1)
- negatives 734C-750B (Box 18, Folder 1)
- negatives 750C-770A (Box 19, Folder 1)
- negatives 770B-806B (Box 20, Folder 1)
- negatives 806C-857C (Box 21, Folder 1)
- negatives 858A-899A (Box 22, Folder 1)
- negatives 900A-945C (Box 23, Folder 1)
- negatives 949A-973A (Box 24, Folder 1)
- negatives 975A-1012D (Box 25, Folder 1)
- negatives 1012E-1050Z (Box 26, Folder 1)
- negatives 1050AA-1098E (Box 27, Folder 1)
- negatives 1098F-1134C (Box 28, Folder 1)
- negatives 1135A-1186C (Box 29, Folder 1)
- negatives 1186D-1257A (Box 30, Folder 1)
- negatives 1257B-1294F (Box 31, Folder 1)
- negatives 1294G-1337 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- negatives 1337-1373G (Box 33, Folder 1)
- negatives 1373D-1417B (Box 34, Folder 1)
- negatives 1418-1454 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- negatives 1455-1494B (Box 36, Folder 1)
- negatives 1494C-1534B (Box 37, Folder 1)
- negatives 1535-1564 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- negatives 1565-1614 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- negatives 1614C-1647G (Box 40, Folder 1)
- negatives 1647H-1683 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- negatives 1684-1730 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- negatives 1732-1804 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- negatives 1805-1857C (Box 44, Folder 1)
- negatives 1857D-1862A (Box 45, Folder 1)
- negatives 1863-1890 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- negatives 1891A-1935 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- negatives 1936-1985 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- negatives 1985C-2034A (Box 49, Folder 1)
- negatives 2034B-2093 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- negatives 2094C-2145 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- negatives 2164A-2226B (Box 52, Folder 1)
- negatives 2227-2287E (Box 53, Folder 1)
- negatives 2288-2345 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- negatives 2346-2402 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- negatives 2403-2415HHH (Box 56, Folder 1)
- negatives 2416-2479 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- negatives 2480-2549B (Box 58, Folder 1)
- negatives 2550-2607 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- negatives 2608A-2647 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- negatives 2648-2691E (Box 61, Folder 1)
- negatives 2691F-2737 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- negatives 2738/2739-2781 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- negatives 2782A-2834 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- negatives 2837-2894A (Box 65, Folder 1)
- negatives 2894B-2958 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- negatives 2959-2999A (Box 67, Folder 1)
- negatives 2999B-3053B (Box 68, Folder 1)
- NOS (Box 69, Folder 1)
- negatives 3054-3098 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- negatives 3104B-3139I (Box 71, Folder 1)
- negatives 3140A-3168F (Box 72, Folder 1)
- negatives 3168G-3200D (Box 73, Folder 1)
- negatives 3200E-3224 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- negatives 3225A-3257C-15 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- negatives 3257C-16-3279 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- negatives 3280-3328C (Box 77, Folder 1)
- negatives 3329-3383 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- negatives 3384A-3412 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- negatives 3413A-3446-000 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- negatives 3447-3503 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- negatives 3504-3535C (Box 82, Folder 1)
- negatives 3537-3576/16324 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- negatives 3576/16326-3620 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- negatives 3621-3660D (Box 85, Folder 1)
- negatives 3661-3696 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- negatives 3697A-3740 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- negatives 3741A-3776-3-A (Box 88, Folder 1)
- negatives 3776-3-B-3823 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- negatives 3825-3871C (Box 90, Folder 1)
- negatives 3872-3907C (Box 91, Folder 1)
- negatives 3908A-3943D (Box 92, Folder 1)
- negatives 3944-3992 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- negatives 3993-4047B (Box 94, Folder 1)
- negatives 4047C-4085B (Box 95, Folder 1)
- negatives 4085C-4120 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- negatives 4121-4146I (Box 97, Folder 1)
- negatives 4146J-4178B (Box 98, Folder 1)
- negatives 4179-4252 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- negatives 23676 CI-29923 C10 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- negatives 29923 C11-29939 C23 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- negatives 29940 C1-176-A (Box 102, Folder 1)
- negatives 1BB1-33BB1 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- negatives 694A-1516 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- negatives 1549-1760 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- negatives 1761-1926 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- negatives 1927-4253 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Contact sheets 1857 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Contact sheets 29890 C1-C11 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Contact sheets 29890 C12-C22 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Contact sheets 29890 C23-C33 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Contact sheets 29923 C1-C15 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Contact sheets 29923 C16-C30 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Contact sheets 29923 C31-C39 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Contact sheets 29939 C1-C12 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Contact sheets 29939 C13-C23 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Contact sheets 29940 C1-C11 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Contact sheets 29940 C12-C22 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Contact sheets 29940 C23-C33 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Contact sheets 30046 C1-C3 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Contact sheets 86254 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Contact sheets 86279 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Contact sheets 86348 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Contact sheets 86408 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Contact sheets 86409 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Contact sheets 224A (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Contact sheets 231A (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Contact sheets 236B (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Contact sheets 237B (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Contact sheets 247A (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Contact sheets 247B (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Contact sheets 247C (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Contact sheets 247D (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Contact sheets 247E (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Contact sheets 247F (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Contact sheets 247G (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Contact sheets 247H (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Contact sheets 247J (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Contact sheets 247K (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Contact sheets 247L (1 OF 2) (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Contact sheets 247L (2 OF 2) (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Contact sheets 247M (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Contact sheets 247N (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Contact sheets 247P (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Contact sheets 247R (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Contact sheets 250A (Box 109, Folder 21)
- Contact sheets 250B (Box 109, Folder 22)
- Contact sheets 257C (Box 109, Folder 23)
- Contact sheets 257H (Box 109, Folder 24)
- Contact sheets 257J (Box 109, Folder 25)
- Contact sheets 257L (1 OF 2) (Box 109, Folder 26)
- Contact sheets 257L (2 OF 2) (Box 109, Folder 27)
- Contact sheets 257M (Box 109, Folder 28)
- Contact sheets 259A (Box 109, Folder 29)
- Contact sheets 261F (Box 109, Folder 30)
- Contact sheets 262B (Box 109, Folder 31)
- Contact sheets 276B (Box 109, Folder 32)
- Contact sheets 282A (Box 109, Folder 33)
- Contact sheets 297A (Box 109, Folder 34)
- Contact sheets 297C (Box 109, Folder 35)
- Contact sheets 312A (Box 109, Folder 36)
- Contact sheets 314C (Box 109, Folder 37)
- Contact sheets 328B (Box 109, Folder 38)
- Contact sheets 340A (Box 109, Folder 39)
- Contact sheets 345A (Box 109, Folder 40)
- Contact sheets 353B (Box 109, Folder 41)
- Contact sheets 353C (Box 109, Folder 42)
- Contact sheets 362B (Box 109, Folder 43)
- Contact sheets 369C (Box 109, Folder 44)
- Contact sheets 381A (Box 109, Folder 45)
- Contact sheets 381B (Box 109, Folder 46)
- Contact sheets 386G (Box 109, Folder 47)
- Contact sheets 395K (Box 109, Folder 48)
- Contact sheets 414A (Box 109, Folder 49)
- Contact sheets 425A (Box 109, Folder 50)
- Contact sheets 426A (Box 109, Folder 51)
- Contact sheets 444A (Box 109, Folder 52)
- Contact sheets 447A (Box 109, Folder 53)
- Contact sheets 449A (Box 109, Folder 54)
- Contact sheets 449B (Box 109, Folder 55)
- Contact sheets 449C (Box 109, Folder 56)
- Contact sheets 449D (Box 109, Folder 57)
- Contact sheets 449E (Box 109, Folder 58)
- Contact sheets 449F (1 OF 2) (Box 109, Folder 59)
- Contact sheets 449F (2 OF 2) (Box 109, Folder 60)
- Contact sheets 449G (Box 109, Folder 61)
- Contact sheets 449H (Box 109, Folder 62)
- Contact sheets 449J (Box 109, Folder 63)
- Contact sheets 449k (Box 109, Folder 64)
- Contact sheets 452A (Box 109, Folder 65)
- Contact sheets 460A (Box 109, Folder 66)
- Contact sheets 460B (Box 109, Folder 67)
- Contact sheets 460C (Box 109, Folder 68)
- Contact sheets 460D (Box 109, Folder 69)
- Contact sheets 460E (Box 109, Folder 70)
- Contact sheets 460F (Box 109, Folder 71)
- Contact sheets 479A (Box 109, Folder 72)
- Contact sheets 484A (Box 109, Folder 73)
- Contact sheets 485D (Box 109, Folder 74)
- Contact sheets 502A (Box 109, Folder 75)
- Contact sheets 503A (Box 109, Folder 76)
- Contact sheets 529A (Box 109, Folder 77)
- Contact sheets 529E (Box 109, Folder 78)
- Contact sheets 539A (Box 109, Folder 79)
- Contact sheets 545A (Box 109, Folder 80)
- Contact sheets 572C (Box 109, Folder 81)
- Contact sheets 583B (Box 109, Folder 82)
- Contact sheets 597A (Box 109, Folder 83)
- Contact sheets 604A (Box 109, Folder 84)
- Contact sheets 614EE (Box 109, Folder 85)
- Contact sheets 616A (Box 109, Folder 86)
- Contact sheets 641B (Box 109, Folder 87)
- Contact sheets 647B (Box 109, Folder 88)
- Contact sheets 647J (Box 109, Folder 89)
- Contact sheets 647K (Box 109, Folder 90)
- Contact sheets 655A (Box 109, Folder 91)
- Contact sheets 658A (Box 109, Folder 92)
- Contact sheets 661A (Box 109, Folder 93)
- Contact sheets 661B (Box 109, Folder 94)
- Contact sheets 673B (Box 109, Folder 95)
- Contact sheets 673F (Box 109, Folder 96)
- Contact sheets 674C (Box 109, Folder 97)
- Contact sheets 681B (Box 109, Folder 98)
- Contact sheets 681G (Box 109, Folder 99)
- Contact sheets 684A (Box 109, Folder 100)
- Contact sheets 734A (Box 109, Folder 101)
- Contact sheets 758C (Box 109, Folder 102)
- Contact sheets 787A (Box 109, Folder 103)
- Contact sheets 860A (Box 109, Folder 104)
- Contact sheets 860B (Box 109, Folder 105)
- Contact sheets 883A (Box 109, Folder 106)
- Contact sheets 886A (Box 109, Folder 107)
- Contact sheets 920A (Box 109, Folder 108)
- Contact sheets 920C (Box 109, Folder 109)
- Contact sheets 923A (Box 109, Folder 110)
- Contact sheets 984A (Box 109, Folder 111)
- Contact sheets 984B (Box 109, Folder 112)
- Contact sheets 984C (Box 109, Folder 113)
- Contact sheets 984D (Box 109, Folder 114)
- Contact sheets 984E (Box 109, Folder 115)
- Contact sheets 984F (Box 109, Folder 116)
- Contact sheets 984G (Box 109, Folder 117)
- Contact sheets 984H (Box 109, Folder 118)
- Contact sheets 984J (Box 109, Folder 119)
- Contact sheets 984K (Box 109, Folder 120)
- Contact sheets 984L (Box 109, Folder 121)
- Contact sheets 984M (Box 109, Folder 122)
- Contact sheets 984N (Box 109, Folder 123)
- Contact sheets 984P (Box 109, Folder 124)
- Contact sheets 984R (Box 109, Folder 125)
- Contact sheets 984S (Box 109, Folder 126)
- Contact sheets 984T (Box 109, Folder 127)
- Contact sheets 984U (Box 109, Folder 128)
- Contact sheets 984V (Box 109, Folder 129)
- Contact sheets 984W (Box 109, Folder 130)
- Contact sheets 984X (Box 109, Folder 131)
- Contact sheets 987A (Box 109, Folder 132)
- Contact sheets 1013C (Box 109, Folder 133)
- Contact sheets 1028A (Box 109, Folder 134)
- Contact sheets 1028B (Box 109, Folder 135)
- Contact sheets 1028C (Box 109, Folder 136)
- Contact sheets 1028D (Box 109, Folder 137)
- Contact sheets 1028E (Box 109, Folder 138)
- Contact sheets 1039A (Box 109, Folder 139)
- Contact sheets 1117A (Box 109, Folder 140)
- Contact sheets 1129A (Box 109, Folder 141)
- Contact sheets 1182A (Box 109, Folder 142)
- Contact sheets 1202A (Box 109, Folder 143)
- Contact sheets 1272A (Box 109, Folder 144)
- Contact sheets 1274A (Box 109, Folder 145)
- Contact sheets 1278A (Box 109, Folder 146)
- Contact sheets 1278B (Box 109, Folder 147)
- Contact sheets 1300A (Box 109, Folder 148)
- Contact sheets 1306A (Box 109, Folder 149)
- Contact sheets 1306B (Box 109, Folder 150)
- Contact sheets 1323A (Box 109, Folder 151)
- Contact sheets 1352B (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Contact sheets 1371A (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Contact sheets 1371E (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Contact sheets 1372B (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Contact sheets 1376 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Contact sheets 1403A (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Contact sheets 1403B (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Contact sheets 1403C (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Contact sheets 1411A (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Contact sheets 1422 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Contact sheets 1424A (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Contact sheets 1424B (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Contact sheets 1426A (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Contact sheets 1432A (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Contact sheets 1433A (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Contact sheets 1441 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Contact sheets 1474 (Box 110, Folder 17)
- Contact sheets 1475 (Box 110, Folder 18)
- Contact sheets 1494A (Box 110, Folder 19)
- Contact sheets 1495 (Box 110, Folder 20)
- Contact sheets 1513D (Box 110, Folder 21)
- Contact sheets 1513E (Box 110, Folder 22)
- Contact sheets 1535A (Box 110, Folder 23)
- Contact sheets 1610 (Box 110, Folder 24)
- Contact sheets 1621A (Box 110, Folder 25)
- Contact sheets 1661A (Box 110, Folder 26)
- Contact sheets 1661A (Box 110, Folder 27)
- Contact sheets 1661B (Box 110, Folder 28)
- Contact sheets 1661B (Box 110, Folder 29)
  Scope and Contents
  second folder
- Contact sheets 1661C (Box 110, Folder 30)
- Contact sheets 1661C (Box 110, Folder 31)
- Contact sheets 1661D (Box 110, Folder 32)
- Contact sheets 1661D (Box 110, Folder 33)
- Contact sheets 1715 (Box 110, Folder 34)
- Contact sheets 1738 (Box 110, Folder 35)
- Contact sheets 1743 (Box 110, Folder 36)
- Contact sheets 1828 (Box 110, Folder 37)
- Contact sheets 1871E (Box 110, Folder 38)
- Contact sheets 1882A (Box 110, Folder 39)
- Contact sheets 1882B (Box 110, Folder 40)
- Contact sheets 1882C (Box 110, Folder 41)
- Contact sheets 1882D (Box 110, Folder 42)
- Contact sheets 1882E (Box 110, Folder 43)
- Contact sheets 1882F (Box 110, Folder 44)
- Contact sheet 1889A (Box 110, Folder 45)
- Contact sheets 1889B (Box 110, Folder 46)
- Contact sheets 1889C (Box 110, Folder 47)
- Contact sheets 1889D (Box 110, Folder 48)
- Contact sheets 1889E (Box 110, Folder 49)
- Contact sheets 1889F (Box 110, Folder 50)
- Contact sheets 1892 (Box 110, Folder 51)
- Contact sheets 1901 (Box 110, Folder 52)
- Contact sheets 1906A (Box 110, Folder 53)
- Contact sheets 1933 (Box 110, Folder 54)
- Contact sheets 1942A (Box 110, Folder 55)
- Contact sheets 1942B (Box 110, Folder 56)
- Contact sheets 1993 (Box 110, Folder 57)
- Contact sheets 1997 (Box 110, Folder 58)
- Contact sheets 2013A (Box 110, Folder 59)
- Contact sheets 2043 (Box 110, Folder 60)
- Contact sheets 2051 (Box 110, Folder 61)
- Contact sheets 2053A (Box 110, Folder 62)
- Contact sheets 2059 (Box 110, Folder 63)
- Contact sheets 2062 (Box 110, Folder 64)
- Contact sheets 2066 (Box 110, Folder 65)
- Contact sheets 2087 (Box 110, Folder 66)
- Contact sheets 2115C (Box 110, Folder 67)
- Contact sheets 2115D (Box 110, Folder 68)
- 2125 (Box 110, Folder 69)
- Contact sheets 2142 (Box 110, Folder 70)
- Contact sheets 2149 (Box 110, Folder 71)
- Contact sheets 2154A (Box 110, Folder 72)
- Contact sheets 2154B (Box 110, Folder 73)
- Contact sheets 2154C (Box 110, Folder 74)
- Contact sheets 2158 (Box 110, Folder 75)
- Contact sheets 2159 (Box 110, Folder 76)
- Contact sheets 2203 (Box 110, Folder 77)
- Contact sheets 2216 (Box 110, Folder 78)
- Contact sheets 2240 (Box 110, Folder 79)
- Contact sheets 2256 (Box 110, Folder 80)
- Contact sheets 2262 (Box 110, Folder 81)
- Contact sheets 2274 (Box 110, Folder 82)
- Contact sheets 2281 (Box 110, Folder 83)
- Contact sheets 2288 (Box 110, Folder 84)
- Contact sheets 2290 (Box 110, Folder 85)
- Contact sheets 2309A (Box 110, Folder 86)
- Contact sheets 2309B (Box 110, Folder 87)
- Contact sheets 2327 B1 (Box 110, Folder 88)
- Contact sheets 2327 B2 (Box 110, Folder 89)
- Contact sheets 2327C (Box 110, Folder 90)
- Contact sheets 2354 (Box 110, Folder 91)
- Contact sheets 2376 (Box 110, Folder 92)
- Contact sheets 2406 (Box 110, Folder 93)
- Contact sheets 2409 (Box 110, Folder 94)
- Contact sheets 2412 (Box 110, Folder 95)
- Contact sheets 2425B (Box 110, Folder 96)
- Contact sheets 2429 (Box 110, Folder 97)
- Contact sheets 2431A (Box 110, Folder 98)
- Contact sheets 2431B (Box 110, Folder 99)
- Contact sheets 2438 (Box 110, Folder 100)
- Contact sheets 2439A (Box 110, Folder 101)
- Contact sheets 2439B (Box 110, Folder 102)
- Contact sheets 2440A (Box 110, Folder 103)
- Contact sheets 2440B (Box 110, Folder 104)
- Contact sheets 2440C (Box 110, Folder 105)
- Contact sheets 2440D (Box 110, Folder 106)
- Contact sheets 2466 (Box 110, Folder 107)
- Contact sheets 2478 (Box 110, Folder 108)
- Contact sheets 2498A (Box 110, Folder 109)
- Contact sheets 2498B (Box 110, Folder 110)
- Contact sheets 2509 (Box 110, Folder 111)
- Contact sheets 2512 (Box 110, Folder 112)
- Contact sheets 2513A (Box 110, Folder 113)
- Contact sheets 2513B (Box 110, Folder 114)
- Contact sheets 2548A (Box 110, Folder 115)
- Contact sheets 2548B (Box 110, Folder 116)
- Contact sheets 2582A (Box 110, Folder 117)
- Contact sheets 2582B (Box 110, Folder 118)
- Contact sheets 2611 (Box 110, Folder 119)
- Contact sheets 2633 (Box 110, Folder 120)
- Contact sheets 2651A (Box 110, Folder 121)
- Contact sheets 2651B (Box 110, Folder 122)
- Contact sheets 2663A (Box 110, Folder 123)
- Contact sheets 2679 (Box 110, Folder 124)
- Contact sheets 2688C (Box 110, Folder 125)
- Contact sheets 2688D (Box 110, Folder 126)
- Contact sheets 2688E (Box 110, Folder 127)
- Contact sheets 2691A (Box 110, Folder 128)
- Contact sheets 2691B (Box 110, Folder 129)
- Contact sheets 2691C (Box 110, Folder 130)
- Contact sheets 2300A (Box 110, Folder 131)
- Contact sheets 2752 (Box 110, Folder 132)
- Contact sheets 2759A (Box 110, Folder 133)
- Contact sheets 2770A (Box 110, Folder 134)
- Contact sheets 2770E (Box 110, Folder 135)
- Contact sheets 2770F (Box 110, Folder 136)
- Contact sheets 2770G (Box 110, Folder 137)
- Contact sheets 2775A (Box 110, Folder 138)
- Contact sheets 2779 (Box 110, Folder 139)
- Contact sheets 2885A (Box 110, Folder 140)
- Contact sheets 2917A (Box 110, Folder 141)
- Contact sheets 2917B (Box 110, Folder 142)
- Contact sheets 2923A (Box 110, Folder 143)
- Contact sheets 2935 (Box 110, Folder 144)
- Contact sheets 2952 (Box 110, Folder 145)
- Contact sheets 2961A (Box 110, Folder 146)
- Contact sheets 2961B (Box 110, Folder 147)
- Contact sheets 2966A (Box 110, Folder 148)
- Contact sheets 2970A (Box 110, Folder 149)
- Contact sheets 2970B (Box 110, Folder 150)
- Contact sheets 2984 (Box 110, Folder 151)
- Contact sheets 2986A (Box 110, Folder 152)
- Contact sheets 3003A (Box 110, Folder 153)
- Contact sheets 3004 (Box 110, Folder 154)
- Contact sheets 3025A (Box 110, Folder 155)
- Contact sheets 3046A (Box 110, Folder 156)
- Contact sheets 3062 (Box 110, Folder 157)
- Contact sheets 3081 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Contact sheets 3135 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Contact sheets 3136A (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Contact sheets 3157A (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Contact sheets 3157B (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Contact sheets 3157D (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Contact sheets 3157F (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Contact sheets 3160 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Contact sheets 3164 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Contact sheets 3166A (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Contact sheets 3168A (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Contact sheets 3168B (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Contact sheets 3168F (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Contact sheets 3170 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Contact sheets 3172A (Box 111, Folder 15)
- Contact sheets 3172B (Box 111, Folder 16)
- Contact sheets 3284A (Box 111, Folder 17)
- Contact sheets 3289a (Box 111, Folder 18)
- Contact sheets 3308 (Box 111, Folder 19)
- Contact sheets 3319a (Box 111, Folder 20)
- Contact sheet 3344 (Box 111, Folder 21)
- Contact sheets 3367A (Box 111, Folder 22)
- Contact sheets 3396A (Box 111, Folder 23)
- Contact sheets 3445 (Box 111, Folder 24)
- Contact sheets 3446A (Box 111, Folder 25)
- Contact sheets 3446C (Box 111, Folder 26)
- Contact sheets 3504-16185 (Box 111, Folder 27)
- Contact sheets 3522A (Box 111, Folder 28)
- Contact sheets 3522B (Box 111, Folder 29)
- Contact sheets 3525 (Box 111, Folder 30)
- Contact sheets 3538A (Box 111, Folder 31)
- Contact sheets 3538B (Box 111, Folder 32)
- Contact sheets 3538C (Box 111, Folder 33)
- Contact sheets 3538D (Box 111, Folder 34)
- Contact sheets 3538E (Box 111, Folder 35)
- Contact sheets 3538F (Box 111, Folder 36)
- Contact sheets 3566 (Box 111, Folder 37)
- Contact sheets 3567 (Box 111, Folder 38)
- Contact sheets 3572a (Box 111, Folder 39)
- Contact sheet 3577-16338 (Box 111, Folder 40)
- Contact sheets 3584A (Box 111, Folder 41)
- Contact sheet 3684B (Box 111, Folder 42)
- Contact sheets 3595 (Box 111, Folder 43)
- Contact sheets 3632 (Box 111, Folder 44)
- Contact sheets 3657 (Box 111, Folder 45)
- Contact sheets 3661 (Box 111, Folder 46)
- Contact sheets 3699A (Box 111, Folder 47)
- Contact sheets 3699C (Box 111, Folder 48)
- Contact sheets 3709 (Box 111, Folder 49)
- Contact sheets 3734B (Box 111, Folder 50)
- Contact sheets 3764 (Box 111, Folder 51)
- Contact sheets 3768 (Box 111, Folder 52)
- Contact sheets 3771 (Box 111, Folder 53)
- Contact sheets 3776-2-CHB (Box 111, Folder 54)
- Contact sheets 3778 (Box 111, Folder 55)
- Contact sheets 3799 (Box 111, Folder 56)
- Contact sheets 3810 (Box 111, Folder 57)
- Contact sheets 3835A (Box 111, Folder 58)
- Contact sheets 3835B (Box 111, Folder 59)
- Contact sheets 3835C (Box 111, Folder 60)